Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
Hi guys.
嗨，大家好。
My name is Katrin and today we're talking about something that is a little bit private.
我是Katrin，今天我们要聊一个有点私密的话题。
That's right, but very necessary to learn in English because it's very, very useful.
没错，但学英语时非常必要，因为它非常非常有用。
That's right.
没错。
So we're talking about clothing, more specifically underwear.
所以我们要聊的是衣服，更具体地说，是内衣。
So the clothes you wear under your clothes.
就是你穿在衣服里面的衣服。
That's right.
没错。
Okay, so let's just jump into the dialogue.
好，那我们就直接进入对话吧。
Let's see what happens today and we'll be back in a bit.
看看今天发生了什么，我们一会儿回来。
Lily, I found a pair of men's boxers in the laundry machine this morning.
Lily，今天早上我在洗衣机里发现了一条男士平角内裤。
What?
什么？
That's weird.
真奇怪。
Are they your boyfriend's?
是你男朋友的吗？
Nah, Kevin only wears briefs.
不，Kevin只穿三角内裤。
Plus, this pair is extra small.
而且，这条是超小号的。
What do they look like?
它们长什么样？
They're light blue with thin pink stripes.
浅蓝色带细粉色条纹。
Oh, and there's Snoopy on it, which is hilarious.
哦，上面还有史努比，太搞笑了。
Those are my undies.
那是我的内裤。
All right, so a lot of great vocab there.
好了，这里有很多很棒的词汇。
Let's take a look at that now on Language Takeaway.
我们现在在“语言要点”环节来看看。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
So the first thing we have here in Language Takeaway is actually very interesting, Marco,
所以我们在“语言要点”里第一个要讲的东西其实很有趣，Marco，
because we don't say one underwear or one boxers.
因为我们不说“一件内衣”或“一条平角内裤”。
We say a pair of, just like pants, a pair of pants or a pair of underwear.
我们说“一条”，就像裤子一样，“一条裤子”或“一条内裤”。
A pair of pants, a pair of shorts, socks.
一条裤子、一条短裤、袜子。
The same thing goes for underwear.
内衣也是一样。
So I really don't know why because it's one piece.
我真的不知道为什么，因为它是一件东西。
So are pants, but basically you have two holes, two places for your legs.
裤子也是，但基本上你有两个洞，两个放腿的地方。
So anything with your legs, your socks, your shoes, your pants, your underwear, you need
所以任何和腿有关的东西，你的袜子、鞋子、裤子、内裤，你都需要
a pair because you've got both sides, left and right.
“一条”，因为你有两边，左边和右边。
Okay.
好的。
All right, so you got a pair of men's boxers.
好，所以你有一条男士平角内裤。
Now before we describe the underwear part, let's take a look at this other machine, a
在我们描述内衣部分之前，我们先看看另一个机器，
laundry machine.
洗衣机。
Okay, so you know what a machine is.
好，你知道机器是什么。
It's usually something that uses electricity to help us with a task or a job.
它通常是用电来帮助我们完成某项任务或工作的东西。
But a laundry machine is special because it helps us clean our laundry.
但洗衣机很特别，因为它帮我们洗衣服。
What kind of things are laundry?
什么是“laundry”？
So anything that's your clothes.
就是你的任何衣服。
So basically it's also called a washing machine, right?
所以基本上它也叫“washing machine”，对吧？
So laundry machine or washing machine, same thing.
所以“laundry machine”或“washing machine”，一回事。
It uses water and soap to wash your clothes.
它用水和肥皂来洗你的衣服。
That's right.
没错。
Okay, so now let's get into the type of underwear here, specifically for men.
好，现在我们来看看内衣的类型，特别是男士的。
Usually we have boxers, boxer shorts.
通常我们有平角内裤、平角短裤。
That's right.
没错。
So shorts means that they're not long, they're short.
所以“shorts”意思是它们不长，是短的。
So boxers or boxer shorts as you say are usually pretty loose.
所以平角内裤或平角短裤通常很宽松。
They're not very tight and they're longer than the other kinds of underwear we have.
它们不太紧，而且比其他类型的内衣长。
Okay, so boxers are a type of underwear that men wear under their clothes and as you say
好，所以平角内裤是男士穿在衣服下面的一种内衣，就像你说的，
they're pretty much shorts.
它们基本上是短裤。
But they're called boxers or you can call them boxer shorts.
但它们叫“boxers”或者你可以叫它们“boxer shorts”。
Now I guess the classic or the common form of men's underwear are called briefs.
我想经典或常见的男士内衣形式叫“briefs”。
Briefs, now these are smaller than boxers and they're tighter.
三角内裤，这些比平角内裤小，而且更紧。
And they are usually made out of some kind of material that stretches.
它们通常由某种有弹性的材料制成。
You can pull them a little bit.
你可以稍微拉一下。
And this is again a smaller version, well a smaller kind of underwear.
这又是更小的版本，嗯，更小的一种内衣。
That's right.
没错。
So boxers are more like shorts, briefs are kind of and briefs are not really shorts.
所以平角内裤更像短裤，三角内裤有点像，三角内裤不完全是短裤。
They're more like, I guess kind of like a swimming suit.
它们更像，我想有点像泳衣。
They look like a bathing suit bottom for men.
它们看起来像男士泳裤的下半部分。
Okay, now, that's it, right?
好，就这样，对吧？
Okay, undies.
好，“undies”。
Okay, so both these things we could actually describe as undies.
好，所以这两种东西我们都可以描述为“undies”。
That's right.
没错。
So undies is a common spoken language way of saying underwear.
所以“undies”是“underwear”的口语说法。
Okay, so it's very casual and it's usually something that we say with our family or friends.
好，所以它很随意，通常是我们和家人或朋友说的。
Especially moms like to say this with their kids.
特别是妈妈喜欢对孩子这么说。
Alright, honey, I'm going to buy you some new undies this week.
好的，亲爱的，这周我给你买些新内裤。
And of course, as a child, you feel very embarrassed.
当然，作为孩子，你会觉得很尴尬。
Undies is a way to say underwear.
“Undies”是“underwear”的一种说法。
Alright.
好的。
Okay, so that's all the vocab that we have for you on Language Takeaway.
好，这就是我们在“语言要点”环节为你准备的所有词汇。
Why don't we listen to our dialogue again and we'll be back in a bit with Fluency Builder.
我们为什么不重新听一遍对话，然后一会儿在“流利度提升”环节回来。
Lily, I found a pair of men's boxers in the laundry machine this morning.
Lily，今天早上我在洗衣机里发现了一条男士平角内裤。
What?
什么？
That's weird.
真奇怪。
Are they your boyfriend's?
是你男朋友的吗？
Nah, Kevin only wears briefs.
不是，凯文只穿平角内裤。
Plus, this pair is extra small.
而且，这条是超小号的。
What do they look like?
它们长什么样？
They're light blue with thin pink stripes.
是浅蓝色的，带有细粉色条纹。
Oh, and there's Snoopy on it, which is hilarious.
哦，上面还有史努比，挺搞笑的。
Those are my undies.
那是我的内裤。
Alright, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So now let's take a look at some descriptive words in Fluency Builder.
现在让我们看看“流利度构建”里的一些描述性词汇。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建。
Alright, so as you said, Marco, we have a lot of great phrases today and some words
好的，就像你说的，马可，我们今天有很多好用的短语和一些词汇，
for describing underwear.
用来描述内衣。
And you can describe other things with these words as well.
你也可以用这些词来描述其他东西。
The first one we have is a phrase, extra small.
第一个是一个短语，“超小号”。
Okay, so when you buy underwear, the sizes, you sometimes get small, extra small, large,
好的，买内衣时，尺码有时会分小号、超小号、大号、
medium, but it's just a way of describing how big it is.
中号，但这只是描述大小的一种方式。
Right, so you know the S, the M and the L are small, medium and large.
对，你知道S、M、L分别代表小号、中号和大号。
But if you see the XS, that's extra small, it means it's very small.
但如果你看到XS，那就是超小号，意思是它非常小。
Alright, we also have XL, which is extra large.
好的，我们还有XL，也就是超大号。
That's right.
没错。
Okay, so now that we've described the size, now we're going to describe a little
好了，现在我们描述了尺寸，接下来要描述一下
bit of how they look like, the colors and maybe any characteristics.
它们的外观、颜色，可能还有一些特征。
So the first thing that we see is the color is light blue.
首先我们看到的是颜色是浅蓝色。
Okay, so we've got blue, which is normal blue.
好的，我们有蓝色，就是普通的蓝色。
We have light blue, which is maybe the color of the sky on a beautiful summer day.
还有浅蓝色，可能就像美丽夏日天空的颜色。
There's also, we didn't hear it in today's dialogue, but there's another color, it's
还有另一种颜色，我们今天对话里没提到，那就是
dark blue, which is almost more like purple or black.
深蓝色，它几乎更像紫色或黑色。
That's right.
没错。
So this is the way of describing a color.
所以这是描述颜色的一种方式。
Now it can be for any color except white.
这适用于除了白色以外的任何颜色。
You don't really say light white or dark white.
你不会说“浅白色”或“深白色”。
Yeah, you don't.
对，不会。
So you could say light green, dark green, light orange, dark orange.
所以你可以说浅绿色、深绿色、浅橙色、深橙色。
Okay, and now some characteristics.
好的，现在来说一些特征。
They had some thin pink stripes.
它们有细粉色条纹。
So we have the word here thin.
这里我们有一个词“细”。
So not fat, thin.
不是粗，是细。
Pink we have the color, but what are stripes?
“粉色”是颜色，但“条纹”是什么？
Okay, stripes are a very common design for clothes and you often see stripes, they're
好的，条纹是衣服上很常见的设计，你经常看到条纹，它们
like lines.
就像线条。
And so that means that you have different lines that are pink.
所以意思是上面有不同颜色的粉色线条。
You often see stripes on flags.
你经常在旗帜上看到条纹。
So for example, the American flag has red and white stripes.
比如，美国国旗有红白条纹。
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
So as you said, there are lines and yeah, usually in clothing, you can find maybe shirts
就像你说的，是线条，而且通常在衣服上，你可能会找到
that have vertical stripes or sometimes even horizontal stripes.
有竖条纹或有时甚至横条纹的衬衫。
Yes, but these undies are quite unique.
是的，但这条内裤很独特。
They're very special because they have pink stripes.
它们很特别，因为有粉色条纹。
That's right.
没错。
Okay, so that's all the language we have for you.
好了，这就是我们为你准备的所有语言点。
Why don't we listen to our dialogue one last time and we'll be back in a little bit.
我们最后再听一遍对话，然后一会儿回来。
Lily I found a pair of men's boxers in the laundry machine this morning.
莉莉，我今天早上在洗衣机里发现了一条男士平角内裤。
What?
什么？
That's weird.
真奇怪。
Are they your boyfriend's?
是你男朋友的吗？
Nah, Kevin only wears briefs.
不是，凯文只穿平角内裤。
Plus this pair is extra small.
而且这条是超小号的。
What do they look like?
它们长什么样？
They're light blue with thin pink stripes.
是浅蓝色的，带有细粉色条纹。
Oh, and there's Snoopy on it, which is hilarious.
哦，上面还有史努比，挺搞笑的。
Those are my undies.
那是我的内裤。
All right, so in this case, we're talking about men's boxer shorts because there was
好的，在这个例子里，我们说的是男士平角内裤，因为
a confusion about the boyfriend.
关于男朋友的事有误会。
But women also wear boxer shorts.
但女性也穿平角内裤。
It's very popular now among women.
现在在女性中很流行。
Yeah, it is.
是的，确实如此。
It's usually something that women wear over their underwear.
通常女性会把它穿在内裤外面。
Women don't really wear boxer shorts as underwear.
女性一般不把平角内裤当内衣穿。
Women's underwear is smaller.
女性的内衣更小。
It's like men's briefs.
就像男士的平角内裤。
Okay, so if a girl wears boxers and it's usually for maybe if they're just around the house
好的，所以如果女孩穿平角内裤，通常可能是她们在家
and you don't want to wear pants and you don't want to wear shorts, you can just wear a pair
不想穿裤子也不想穿短裤时，就可以穿一条
of comfortable boxer shorts.
舒适的平角内裤。
Exactly, like they wear pajamas.
没错，就像穿睡衣一样。
And actually, I think a lot of girls also use boxer shorts as pajamas, right?
实际上，我觉得很多女孩也把平角内裤当睡衣穿，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
They're comfortable and they're light and they're usually made from cotton, which is
它们很舒适、很轻，而且通常由棉制成，这是
a nice material to sleep in.
一种适合睡觉的好材料。
Now when we're talking about briefs, there is also another way that I've heard that they're
当我们说到平角内裤时，我还听说过另一种叫法，
called sometimes, a more maybe funny way of calling them.
可能更有趣的叫法。
Some people say they're called tidy whities.
有些人说它们叫“小白内裤”。
That's right.
没错。
This is usually something we say to joke because in America, at least, many men like to wear,
这通常是我们开玩笑时说的，因为在美国，至少很多男人喜欢穿，
young men like to wear boxers.
年轻男人喜欢穿平角内裤。
So they call briefs tidy whities.
所以他们把三角内裤叫做“小白内裤”。
Because usually, briefs are just white.
因为通常三角内裤就是白色的。
They're plain.
它们很朴素。
They don't have any design or any other color.
没有任何图案或其他颜色。
No, they're plain and they're white usually or gray and they're tight, not like boxers.
不，它们很朴素，通常是白色或灰色，而且紧身，不像平角内裤。
So the casual name, this is not something you want to say to your English teacher, by
所以这个随意的叫法，顺便说一句，这不是你想跟英语老师说的话，
the way.
顺便说一句。
The casual name or the funny name is tidy whities.
这个随意的名字或搞笑的名字就是“小白内裤”。
Tidy whities.
“小白内裤”。
Actually, this is very interesting because with newer generations, I think men are wearing
实际上，这很有趣，因为在新一代人中，我觉得男人现在穿
boxers instead of briefs.
平角内裤而不是三角内裤。
Before, I think the only option was briefs.
以前，我觉得唯一的选择就是三角内裤。
But now boxers have grown more and more popular and I think when you're a little kid, your
但现在平角内裤越来越流行，而且我觉得当你还是小孩时，你
mom always buys you little briefs and everything.
妈妈总是给你买小三角内裤之类的。
But then when you're a teenager, I think you just switch over to boxers.
但当你成为青少年时，我觉得你就会换成平角内裤。
It's not as cool anymore to wear briefs.
穿三角内裤不再那么酷了。
I think it's the whole fact of how kids sometimes dress with saggy or baggy pants and so they
我觉得这跟孩子们有时穿松垮或宽松的裤子有关，所以他们
like to show their boxers underneath for some reason.
不知为什么喜欢露出里面的平角内裤。
I don't really understand it.
我其实不太理解。
But if you do, let us know.
但如果你懂，请告诉我们。
Our website is EnglishPod.com.
我们的网站是EnglishPod.com。
We're going to have all the vocabulary and stuff on the website so check it out.
我们会在网站上放所有词汇和内容，所以去看看吧。
All right.
好的。
We'll see you guys there.
我们那儿见。
Bye.
再见。
EnglishPod YouTube